<root>
<Anant> Agarwal</Anant>
<anant_agarwal@gatech.edu>							 	    337123 Georgia Tech Station</anant_agarwal@gatech.edu>
<(404)> 310-0207											         Atlanta, GA 30332</(404)>
<OBJECTIVE:> To apply my skills in computer science and economics to obtain an entry level internship.</OBJECTIVE:>
<></>
<EDUCATION></EDUCATION>
<Georgia>	 Institute of Technology, Atlanta, GA					                August 2009-Present</Georgia>
<Candidate,> Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, Economics minor (expected graduation: May 2013) </Candidate,>
<Languages> spoken: Hindi, English</Languages>
<Most> Recent Semester GPA 3.8, Dean’s List</Most>
<Georgia> Tech Lorraine- Study Abroad in Metz, France				May 2011-August 2011</Georgia>
<Travelled> 10 countries in continental Europe, completing Georgia Tech coursework while experiencing different cultures.</Travelled>
<></>
<WORK> EXPERIENCE</WORK>
<Georgia>	 Institute of Technology- Peer Leader						 January 2011-Present</Georgia>
<Resident> Assistant in Freshmen Dorms managing a floor of 40 people and helping a community of 200. </Resident>
<Supporting> large scale move-ins and move-outs supporting over 2000 people.</Supporting>
<Fostering> community and communicating effectively with over 400 people in the area teaching time management, organization and increasing communication skills and managerial skills by providing academic resources and planning events to provide holistic development for incoming freshmen.</Fostering>
<Performing> duty shifts supporting around 200 freshmen for emergencies, help after hours.</Performing>
<></>
<Undergraduate> Research, Georgia Institute of Technology- Public Policy     September 2010- December 2010</Undergraduate>
<Performed> research for Professor John Walsh (Public Policy) providing 300 data samples for his project.</Performed>
<Searched> for articles, papers and provided contact information of relevant scientists to help participate in a survey which Professor Walsh was conducting learning statistical analysis and developing technical analysis skills.</Searched>
<>	</>
<Cinecita>	 Private Limited, Mumbai, India- Technical intern                            	             June 2010-August 2010</Cinecita>
<Repaired> over 10 hardware devices including amplifiers, speakers and computers with company engineers learning organizational set-ups in hardware, increasing technical analysis and time management skills.</Repaired>
<Interacted> with technicians and learned about installation processes and demonstrations of projectors.</Interacted>
<></>
<ADAPTS,>	 Georgia Institute of Technology Atlanta, GA – Note taker		           September 2009-Present</ADAPTS,>
<Taking> notes for disabled students learning paying attention to detail and formatting text properly.</Taking>
<></>
<College> of Computing, Georgia Institute of Technology Atlanta, GA – Tutor	                January 2012-Present</College>
<Analyzing> and helping students solve problems along with assisting them in coursework.</Analyzing>
<></>
<SKILLS></SKILLS>
<Software> and IT</Software>
<Microsoft> Word, PowerPoint, Excel, C, C++, Java, HTML, MATLAB, AutoCAD, PHP, MySQL, LINUX</Microsoft>
<Knowledge> of data structures, coding algorithms, GUI design and application in building trees, maps, hash tables, etc.</Knowledge>
<></>
<Electrical> Engineering</Electrical>
<Knowledge> of statistical analysis of digital signals, circuitry, PCBs, soldering, attaching components</Knowledge>
<></>
<Extracurricular> Activities</Extracurricular>
<Community> Service- Tech Beautification Day (Spring 2010), Team buzz (Project Coordinator, Fall 2010),  Service Project(Youth Pride, Spring 2010)</Community>
<></>
<ACTIVITIES/HONORS></ACTIVITIES/HONORS>
<Dean's> List (Fall 2011, Summer 2011, Spring 2010)</Dean's>
<Served> on and captained my Badminton high school varsity team and my state team (in nationals) and was successful in winning 3 major varsity championships. 		September 2003-August 2009</Served>
<Sports> Captain in high school and felicitated for multiple achievements in badminton and academics. </Sports>
<September> 2003-August 2006</September>
</root>
